https://krayden.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Krayden
Krayden
Search Site
Search:
Search Site
Search:
Last updated July 22, 2020
This Privacy Policy has been prepared by Krayden, Inc. (“Krayden,” “us,” our” or “we”), with an address at 1491 W. 124th Avenue, Denver, Colorado 80234. Krayden is committed to protecting your privacy. Our privacy policy, which applies to all users of our website located at www.krayden.com (the “Website”) and the features and functionality thereof (the “Service”), is designed to explain the information we collect and how we use it to provide our services and give users a better experience (“Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into, our Terms and Conditions [see https://krayden.com/terms-and-conditions/].
By accessing and using the Website and/or Service, you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your Personal Information (as defined below) and other information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Types of Information We Collect
We collect both “Personal Information” and “Anonymous Information” about our users. For the purposes of certain data protection laws in jurisdictions outside the U.S., such as the E.U., Krayden is the data controller of Personal Information collected through our Website and the Service.
Personal Information is information that can be used to identify you, directly or indirectly, such as your name, email address, phone number and payment method, as well as information that is linked to such information. “Anonymous Information” is information that cannot be used to identify you and is not linked to information that can be used to do so. It includes passively collected information about your activities on the Service, such as usage data, to the extent that information is not linked to your Personal Information.
Website visitors can access and browse certain portions of the Website without disclosing Personal Information, although, like most website providers, we may passively collect certain information from your devices, such as your IP address and browser information. Please note that you can choose not to provide us with certain information, but this will limit the features of the Service you can access and use. All users who register with Krayden are considered “Registered Customers.”
a. Voluntarily submitted information
We collect information that you provide to us during your use of the Website and/or Service, such as:
Personal Information that you enter when registering for the Service or ordering products, including your full name, email address, phone number, payment method and billing information.
Your communications with us through the Service.
Information you provide in your online account (“Account”) or to customer support.
b. Information collected via technology
We may collect information from your use of the Website and Service, including your hardware model, browser type, operating system and Internet Protocol (“IP”). If you are using a mobile device, Krayden may also receive your unique device identifier, or another unique identifier, and mobile operating system. We may correlate this information with other Personal Information we have about you.
We may also use cookies and URL information to gather information regarding the date and time you used the Service and the information for which you searched and accessed. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your device while you are viewing the Website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your device until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following web browser help file directions.
We may use third party services, such as Google Analytics, to track and analyze data from users of the Service.
If you access our Service via a social media website (e.g., Facebook), your Personal Information may be provided to us by such social media site.
Such Personal Information is required in order for us to provide our Services and Website, without which we would not be able to undertake certain tasks, such as processing and filling orders.
How We Use Your Information
a. Personal Information
We use your Personal Information only for legitimate purposes necessary to operate our Website and provide our Services, such as to:
Register and administer your Account
Complete your purchase transactions
Offer customer support
Send communications and administrative emails
Personalize and tailor the features, performance and support of the Website and Service
Send you promotional/marketing information, newsletters, offers or other information from us or on behalf of our sponsors or partners, with your consent
Provide you with opportunities and functionality that we think would be of particular interest
Improve the quality of the Website and Service and perform internal operations, including monitoring for fraud
Analyze, benchmark and conduct research on user data and interactions with the Service
b. Anonymous Information
We may use Anonymous Information for the following representative purposes:
Improve the Website and Service and customize the user experience, such as by providing targeted useful features and promotions based on the type of products you seek
Aggregate the information collected via Cookies and similar technologies to use in statistical analysis to help us track trends, evaluate the effectiveness of our ads and analyze patterns
How We Share and Disclose Information
We know how important it is to keep your information confidential. We will not rent, sell or share your Personal Information with third parties except as specifically approved by you at the time of disclosure or under the circumstances described in this Privacy Policy.
In addition to using the information collected by us for the purposes described in Section 2 above, we may also share your information as described below. Please review our sharing policy closely, especially with respect to your Personal Information. By becoming a Registered Customer, you agree to allow us to share the Personal Information you provide to us in the ways described below. Your ability to make changes to the information shared is also described below.
a. Service Providers
We share Personal Information with vendors, suppliers, consultants and data and payment processers who perform services on behalf of Krayden, but only if we have in place a written contract requiring them to protect your Personal Information. Krayden has selected companies who maintain high standards with respect to privacy and agree to use the Personal Information only to perform specific services on behalf of Krayden and in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Our service providers are given only the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose Personal Information for their own marketing or other purposes.
b. Compliance with Laws, Law Enforcement and Safety
We may disclose information we have collected about you if required to do so by law or legal process (such as a court order) or if we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is reasonable to comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process (whether or not such disclosure is required by applicable law), or that disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect or defend Krayden’s, or a third party’s, rights or property, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.
c. Anonymous Information
Aggregated Anonymous Information is the combination of your Anonymous Information with the Anonymous Information of other users (“Aggregated Anonymous Information”). Aggregated Anonymous Information does not allow you to be identified or contacted. We may share such Aggregated Anonymous Information with third parties, and, depending on the circumstances, we may or may not charge third parties for such information, or limit the third parties’ use of the same.
d. Business transactions
We may share all or some of your Personal Information with any of our subsidiaries, joint venturers, or other companies under common control, but only if an adequate level of protection is in place to protect your Personal Information. Additionally, in the event we undergo a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. We will take reasonable steps to ensure the security and confidentiality of any of your Personal Information that is transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any entity that acquires us, is merged with us or that acquires our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
International Transfers of Personal Information
Your Personal Information will be maintained and processed by Krayden or its third party service providers, in the U.S. Your Personal Information may also be transferred to our suppliers and representatives in other jurisdictions. Those jurisdictions may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. By providing your Personal Information to the Website or our Service, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to the U.S.
“If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or Switzerland, with respect to transfers of Personal Information to the U.S., Krayden is certified under the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield frameworks developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce, and the European Commission and Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner, respectively, regarding the transfer of Personal Information from the EEA and Switzerland to the U.S. Click Here to view our EU/Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Privacy Policy.”
Your Choices
By becoming a Registered Customer, you will receive certain administrative and transactional communications from us. You may modify or opt out of receiving messages sent for marketing purposes, or certain other communications, by adjusting your Account settings or following the unsubscribe instructions included in each such message, in which case we will not send you further marketing messages. Please note that despite any indicated marketing preferences, we may send you administrative or transactional emails regarding the Website or Service, including, for example, notices of updates to our Privacy Policy.
Individual Rights
You may access, update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information in our custody or control at any time, subject to limited exceptions set forth below. You may revise or delete your Personal Information by adjusting your Account settings or by contacting us directly at privacy@krayden.com. However, please note that we may be required to maintain certain Personal Information, or to maintain certain Personal Information for a period of time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements. When we delete any information, it will be deleted from our active database, but may remain in our archives. We may retain your information for fraud detection or similar purposes. Note that if we have already disclosed some of your Personal Information to third parties, we cannot access that Personal Information any longer and cannot compel the deletion or modification of any such information by the parties to whom we have made those disclosures. Subject to applicable data protection law and the limitations herein, you can also object to the processing and request that we erase or restrict our processing of your Personal Information. Subject to applicable law, you may also have the right to data portability. Where you have given us consent to process your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.
If you are not satisfied with our response, you may have a right to lodge a complaint with the local supervisory authority in those jurisdictions with applicable privacy legislation.
Children
This Website is not directed or intended for children under 16 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit, collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 16, and no part of our Website is targeted to attract anyone under 16. We also do not send e-mail correspondence to anyone who advises that they are under the age of 16. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 16 years of age, we will take steps to remove that user’s Personal Information from our systems and delete the Account. If you are the parent or guardian of a child whom you believe has disclosed Personal Information to us, please contact us at privacy@krayden.com so that we may delete and remove such information from our system.
Security and Data Retention
We are very concerned with safeguarding your information. We have implemented reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration, destruction and access. We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email, text or conspicuous posting on the Website in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as it is consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. Although guaranteed security does not exist either on or off the Internet, we make commercially reasonable efforts to make the collection and security of such information consistent with this Privacy Policy and all applicable laws and regulations.
We will retain your Personal Information only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected, to meet a valid business need and to comply with applicable laws. Your consent to such purpose remains valid after termination of our relationship with you.
Third Party Materials
Krayden may provide links to other websites, or content and materials, that are owned and/or operated by third parties (“Third Party Materials”). Krayden does not investigate or monitor such Third Party Materials, and therefore is not responsible or liable for the same. Moreover, Krayden is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by third party websites, nor are we responsible for the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Website and Service; thus, when you use a link to go from our Website to another third party website, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. We encourage users to read and consider the privacy policies of these other websites before using them.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we advise you otherwise. However, we will not use your Personal Information in a way that is adversely and materially different from the uses described in this Privacy Policy without giving you an opportunity to opt out. Your continued use of the Service after this Privacy Policy has been amended shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy, as amended. We encourage you to bookmark this webpage and review this Privacy Policy regularly.
California Privacy Rights
Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship: (i) a list of the categories of Personal Information, such as name, address, e-mail address, and the type of services provided to that individual, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and (ii) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, California residents can email us at privacy@krayden.com.
Transfer of Personal Information
We may transfer the Personal Information we collect about you to recipients in countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your information to recipients in other countries (such as the U.S.), we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy and will comply with applicable legal requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of Personal Information to recipients in countries other than the one in which you provided the information.
13. Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, you can contact us via email at privacy@krayden.com or send us a letter to Krayden, Inc., Attn: Privacy, 1491 W. 124th Avenue, Denver, Colorado 80234.
RECENT PRODUCT UPDATESExterior Bond and Seal for Wearable Electronic IOTSeptember 15, 2020DOWSIL™ EA-5151 For (ADAS) Advanced Driver Assistance SystemsAugust 26, 2020Henkel Thermal Gel Solutions for Advanced Driver Assistance Systems (ADAS)August 19, 2020Equipment to Dispense Thermal Interface MaterialAugust 12, 2020
Krayden
About Us
Customer Service
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Privacy Shield Privacy Policy
Quality
Need Help?
Copyright © 2017 Krayden, Inc.
Contact
Request a Quote
